A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
The Library of Virginia
42418, 42513 and 42630
100 cu. ft (290 boxes)
Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Clemency Files (pardon files, pardon files-denied) and Restoration of Rights Files (restoration of rights files, and restoration of rights files-denied) contain confidential and privacy-protected information. Access is restricted for 75 years after date of creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
Acquisition Information
Jonathan Young, Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 East Broad Street, Richmond, VA 23219, transferred 18 January 2006 (accession 42418), 27 February 2006 (accession 42513), and 12 April 2006 (accession 42630).
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth has evolved from early colonial times when there existed a Secretary of the Colony. Thomas Nelson held the position of the first Secretary of Virginia in 1776. Early Secretaries were elected by the public. An Act of the General Assembly in 1920 changed the election to a joint vote of the General Assembly. In a 1930 Act the duties of the Secretary were redefined with the Secretary of the Commonwealth serving as the ex officio secretary of the Governor, as custodian of many official State records, and as keeper of the Greater and Lesser Seals of the Commonwealth. The office of the Secretary has gradually acquired other functions, such as: service of out-of-state civil process; appointment and regulation of notaries public; and registration and oversight of lobbyists. The Office became a gubernatorial appointment subsequent to a 1958 Act of the Assembly. The Secretary of the Commonwealth is under the jurisdiction of the Governor's Office. The Secretary is appointed by the Governor for a term of four years. Currently the Secretary of the Commonwealth is responsible for gubernatorial appointments, clemency and restoration of civil rights requests and extraditions. Additional activities include: serving as ex officio Secretary to the Governor; serving as keeper of the seals of the Commonwealth; compiling and publishing the annual Blue Book; commissioning and regulating notary publics, including the publication of a Notary Handbook and conduct of disciplinary hearings; promulgating the lobbying disclosure requirements, registration of lobbyists, and recording of lobbying reports; servicing the civil process of out-of-state defendants and other parties; and authenticating and certifying the records of the courts and of any state agency.
Scope and Content
The Secretary of the Commonwealth, Records, are housed in 290 boxes. The collection is arranged into ten (10) series. Series have been designated for: I Appointment Calendars; II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation; III. Executive Papers; IV. Registration of State Agency Logos, Devices and Slogans; V. Clemency: Pardon Files; VI. Clemency: Pardon Files-Denied; VII. Extradition Requisitions and Renditions; VIII. Notary Public Register; IX. Restoration of Rights Files; and X. Restoration of Rights Files-Denied. These records include affidavits, agendas, appointment calendars, certificates, executive orders, invitations, judicial records, legal files, letters (correspondence), medical records, memorandums, notes, oaths, petitions, transcripts, warrants and writs. These records primarily document the clemency activities of the Warner Administration (2002-2006).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Appointment Calendars: Secretary, 2002-2005
Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Office of the Secretary, 2001-2005
Series III. Executive Papers, 2002-2006
Series IV. Registration of State Agency Logos, Devices and Slogans, 2000-2005
Series V. Clemency: Pardon Files, 2002-2005
Series VI. Clemency: Pardon Files-Denied, 1996-2006
Series VII. Extradition Requisitions and Renditions, 2002-2005
Series VIII. Notary Public Register, 2002-2005
Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006
Series X. Restoration of Rights Files-Denied, 1997, 2003-2006
Contents List
- Series I. Appointment Calendars: Secretary, 2002-2005 (accession 42418)., Extent: 28 folders. (Box 1-4)
  Series contains invitations to Secretary Rimler and related materials pertaining to various events, speaking engagements, meetings and conferences. Secretary Rimler or one of her assistants, Marilyn Mandell or Jo Ann Pulliam, noted on the invitation if she planned to attend. Events attended by Secretary Rimler often include additional registration and contact information. The files are generally arranged chronologically by the date of the engagement, though some invitations/conference material appear to have been filed separately.
  - Invitation Regrets, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part one) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part two) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part one) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part two) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2004 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part one) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Invitations for Anita A. Rimler (part two) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Calendar and Invitations, November 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Calendar and Invitations, January 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, February 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, May 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, June 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, July 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, August 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, September 2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, October 2005 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, November 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, December 2005 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Air Combat Command Tour, 9-10 May 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State (NASS) 2003 Conference, 20-25 February 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State (NASS) 2003 Summer Conference, 25-28 July 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - National Governors Association Management Seminar, 20-22 October 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Conference for Women, 19 November 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Southern Governors Association, 12-14 September 2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Southern Women in Public Service, 15-17 May 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Office of the Secretary, 2001-2005 (accession 42418)., Extent: 2.10 cu. ft. (Box 4-9)
  Series consists of incoming and outgoing correspondence and supporting documentation from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth. The files are arranged alphabetically by topic. The majority of the correspondence consist of constituent correspondence and thank you notes and letters. Notable documents include: memorandum dated 21 July 2002 from Robert M. Blue, Counselor, to Governor Mark R. Warner, summarizing current Virginia law and processes for restoring the right to vote, process for restoring the right to vote in other states, and the policy change recommendations of Blue, Anita Rimler and Secretary of Public Safety, John Marshall; correspondence between Rimler and Delegate Brad Marrs pertaining to his Freedom of Information Act requests concerning the Warner Administration's policies on the restoration of rights (fall 2004); and meeting agendas, notes and documents for HJR 159 (2002), the Joint Subcommittee to Study the Operations, Practices, Duties and Funding of the Commonwealth's Agencies, Boards, Commissions, Councils, and other Governmental Entities.
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, Appointment Application, Analysis and Requirements, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Asian-American Community, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Office of the Attorney General Referrals, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Single Audit Reports, FY 1999 and FY 2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boards/Commissions - Analysis, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board Appointments - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brown vs. Board of Education, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Center for Higher Education Policy Analysis (CHEPA), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - China Trade Mission, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Agency Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Secretary Rimler, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Secretary Rimler, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Secretary Rimler, 2005 and undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Secretary Rimler, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to Secretary Rimler, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to Secretary Rimler, 2004 (part one) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to Secretary Rimler, 2004 (part two) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Secretary Rimler, 2005 and undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Legislative, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 and undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Federal Priorities, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Fellows, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Remarks, Money Committees, 19 August 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gubernatorial Separation Authority, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Legislation - HJR 159 (2002), Joint Subcommittee to Study the Operations, Practices, Duties and Funding of the Commonwealth's Agencies, Boards, Commissions, Councils, and other Governmental Entities, 2002 (part one) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislation - HJR 159 (2002), Joint Subcommittee to Study the Operations, Practices, Duties and Funding of the Commonwealth's Agencies, Boards, Commissions, Councils, and other Governmental Entities, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legislation - HJR 186 (2004), Joint Subcommittee Studying the Disclosure Filings Required by the State and Local Government Conflict of Interest Act, the General Assembly Conflict of Interest Act and the Lobbyist Disclosure and Regulation Act, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State (part one) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State (part two) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - List of Pardons (for 2003) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pardons, undated [Restricted for 75 years from end of Administration (2006)] (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - References, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Agency Reports, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mail Aging Reports, 2002, and 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mail Aging Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Performance Management Annual Report, Fiscal Year 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, 30 June 2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Clemency/ROR Weekly Reports, August 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Notary Public Weekly Reports, August-December 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Service of Process Weekly Reports, September-December 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Requests, February 2002-May 2002 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Requests, May 2002-June 2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Requests, July 2002-August 2002 and undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Restoration of Rights - Delegate Brad Marrs, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Restoration of Rights - Memorandum to Governor Warner from Bob Blue, 21 July 2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Restoration of Rights - Prisoner Issues, 2002 and 2005 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Restoration of Rights - Requests from Legislators, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth Power Point Presentation (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Thank You Letters, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Thank You Notes, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series III. Executive Papers, 2002-2006 (accession 42418)., Extent: 3.68 cu. ft. (Box 10-20)
  Series documents certain official actions of Governor Mark R. Warner during his administration. The files are arranged alphabetically by type of record. Records include gubernatorial appointment announcement letters, lists of appointments submitted to the General Assembly for confirmation, Executive Orders, gubernatorial and judicial appointment oaths, board resignation letters and writs of election. The announcement letters are from the Governor to Secretary of the Commonwealth Rimler requesting that she prepare a commission of appointment. They are arranged chronologically. The lists of appointments were compiled five times a year (during General Assembly session, June, August, October and December) and were submitted to the General Assembly for confirmation. The gubernatorial and judicial appointment oaths and board resignations are arranged by date and then by first letter of surname.
  - Appointment Letters, January-March 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Letters, April-June 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Letters, July-September 2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Letters, October-December 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Letters, January-March 2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Letters, April-May 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Letters, June 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Letters, July 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Letters, August-September 2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Letters, October-December 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Letters, January-March 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Letters, April-May 2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Letters, June 2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Letters, July 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Letters, August-September 2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Letters, October-December 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Letters, January-March 2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Letters, April-June 2005 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Appointment Letters, July 2005 (part one) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Letters, July-September 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Letters, October 2005-January 2006 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Session Appointment List, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Appointment List, June 2002 (2 March 2002-31 May 2002) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Appointment List, August 2002 (1 June 2002-31 July 2002) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Appointment List, October 2002 (1 August 2002-30 September 2002) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Appointment List, December 2002 (1 October 2002-27 November 2002) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Session Appointment List, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Appointment List, June 2003 (23 February 2003-30 May 2003) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Appointment List, August 2003 (1 June 2003-31 July 2003) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Appointment List, October 2003 (1 August 2003-30 September 2003) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Appointment List, December 2003 (1 October 2003-30 November 2003) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Session Appointment List, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Appointment List, June 2004 (27 February 2004-31 May 2004) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Appointment List, August 2004 (1 June 2004-30 July 2004) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Appointment List, October 2004 (1 August 2004-30 September 2004) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Appointment List, December 2004 (1 October 2004-30 November 2004) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Appointment List, June 2005 (28 February 2005-31 May 2005) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Appointment List, August 2005 (1 June 2005-31 July 2005) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Appointment List, October 2005 (1 August 2005-21 September 2005) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Appointment List, December 2005 (22 September 2005-30 November 2005) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Appointment List, January 2006 (1 December 2005-6 January 2006) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Executive Orders, 2002 (No. 1-No. 21) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Executive Orders, 2002 (No. 22-No. 40) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Executive Orders, 2003 (No. 41-No. 59) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Executive Orders, 2004 (No. 60-No. 75) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Executive Orders, 2004 (No. 76-No. 83) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Executive Orders, 2005 (No. 86-No. 97) [Nos. 84-85 missing] (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Executive Orders, 2005 (No. 98-No. 105) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Judicial Oaths, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Judicial Oaths, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Judicial Oaths, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Judicial Oaths, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Judicial Elections, 2002-2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2002, A (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Oaths, 2002, B (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Oaths, 2002, C (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Oaths, 2002, D (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oaths, 2002, E (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Oaths, 2002, F (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Oaths, 2002, G (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Oaths, 2002, H (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2002, I-J (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Oaths, 2002, K-L (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Oaths, 2002, M (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Oaths, 2002, N-Q (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Oaths, 2002, R (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Oaths, 2002, S (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Oaths, 2002, T-V (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Oaths, 2002, W-Z (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Oaths, 2003, A-B (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2003, C (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Oaths, 2003, D-G (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Oaths, 2003, H-L (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Oaths, 2003, M-O (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Oaths, 2003, P-R (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Oaths, 2003, S (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Oaths, 2003, T-Z (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2004, A-B (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Oaths, 2004, C-E (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Oaths, 2004, F-G (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Oaths, 2004, H (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Oaths, 2004, I-L (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Oaths, 2004, M (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2004, N-R (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Oaths, 2004, S (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Oaths, 2004, T-Z (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Oaths, 2005, A-B (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Oaths, 2005, C-G (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Oaths, 2005, H-L (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Oaths, 2005, M-Q (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Oaths, 2005, R-S (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Oaths, 2005, T-Z (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Board Resignations, 2002, A-M (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Board Resignations, 2002, N-Z (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Board Resignations, 2003, A-M (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Board Resignations, 2003, N-Z (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Board Resignations, 2004, A-M (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Board Resignations, 2004, N-Z (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Board Resignations, 2005, A-M (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Board Resignations, 2005, N-Z (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Writs of Election, 2001, 2002, 2005 and 2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Registration of State Agency Logos, Devices and Slogans, 2000-2005 (accession 42418)., Extent: 1.58 cu. ft. (Box 21-25)
  Series documents the registration of logos, state mottos or slogans of state agencies through a form signed by the Secretary of the Commonwealth. This series includes records from the final two years of the administration of Governor James S. Gilmore (2000-2001) and the Warner Administration (2002-2005). The files are arranged chronologically by date filed and registered. Nearly all of the records concern the registration of Virginia Lottery scratch-off tickets and each application form contains an example of the ticket.
  - 21 January 2000-20 April 2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1 June 2000-14 September 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 14 September 2000-5 October 2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 5 December 2000-5 February 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 20 March 2001-26 June 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 2 July 2001-2 October 2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 26 December 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 6 February 2002-24 April 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 22 May 2002-20 June 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 23 July 2002-27 September 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 28 March 2003-16 April 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 30 April 2003-18 June 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 16 July 2003-4 August 2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 27 August 2003-11 November 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 14 November 2003-8 January 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 9 January 2004-20 May 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 20 May 2004-20 August 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 8 September 2004-25 October 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 10 November 2004-21 December 2004 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 17 January 2005-21 March 2005 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 22 March 2005-29 April 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 2 May 2005-11 June 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 29 June 2005-15 August 2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1 September 2005-28 September 2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 10 October 2005-24 October 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Series V. Clemency: Pardon Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42413) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 1.58 cu. ft. (Box 26-30)
  Series documents the pardons granted by Governor Mark R. Warner during his term (2002-2006). Each pardon file usually includes a copy of pardon letter, parole board investigation, Virginia Criminal Information Network reports, Executive Clemency Review Form, recommendation letters or other supporting documentation, and in the case of medical furloughs or pardons, medical records. The files are arranged alphabetically by name. This series contains confidential and privacy-protected information. Access is restricted for 75 years after date of creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
  - Amos, Jr., Tommy L., Simple Pardon, 6 October 2004 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Marvin Lamont (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong, Lesley L., Simple Pardon, 13 December 2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Dan Albert, Simple Pardon, 23 November 2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Berry, Robin Karen, Simple Pardon, 16 April 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Blankenship, Clayton Winfield, Medical Furlough, 11 May 2005 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Boone, Shirl Leondra Wiggins, Simple Pardon, 23 November 2005 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Brady, Michael Joseph, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Carteret, Tommie Jean, Medical Pardon, 2 May 2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cash, Jr., Ronald David, Medical Pardon, 31 May 2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cook, Randolph Willett, Simple Pardon, 21 April 2005 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cothron, Destiney Drumheller, Simple Pardon, 23 November 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Crane, Sr., Michael C., Medical Furlough, 29 July 2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Davidson, Willie Neville, Absolute Pardon, 22 December 2005 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Dozier, Shelia, Simple Pardon, 6 October 2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - English, Thomas F., Simple Pardon, 20 April 2005 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fahmy, Eman, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ford, Raymond, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Gailley, Joan Bennett, Simple Pardon, 23 November 2005 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Gallaher, Jr., Norman Harry, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Garner, David A., Simple Pardon, 21 July 2005 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Greer, Michael David, Simple Pardon, 26 April 2005 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hayden, Brenda, Simple Pardon, 22 December 2005 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins, Troy D., Absolute Pardon, 3 August 2005 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Howard-Waddy, Valerie, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, David Jonathon, Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Jones, William R., Simple Pardon, 13 December 2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Kaull, Dorathia (Dorathy) Starr Whittaker, Simple Pardon, 25 April 2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Langanke, Jr., James, Medical Furlough, 7 May 2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lankford, Monika B., Simple Pardon, 13 October 2003 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - LaPrade, Scott Allan, Simple Pardon, 26 April 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Lare, Gregory S., Simple Pardon, 14 January 2005 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Larkin, Jr., Robert E., Simple Pardon, 23 November 2005 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mack, Stewart William, Simple Pardon, 20 April 2005 (Box 28, Folder 8)